Contact

e7belt@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/elizabeth-belt-b8456852 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Home Care Medical-Surgical Acute Care

Languages

French (Limited Working)
English (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Advanced Cardiac Life Support Basic Cardiac Life Support

Elizabeth Belt

Registered Nurse at Tailored Healthcare Staffing Wilmington, North Carolina Area

Summary

Registered Nurse with Critical Care (Neuroscience ICU, Progressive Care, Stepdown Units) and three years working in the travel nursing industry in the Midwest and on the East Coast. Other care pathways I have experience in include skilled nursing, long-term care, Hospice, and End-of-Life care.

Calm bedside manner in times of a health crisis with focus of ensuring individual's safety, comfort, and dignity

Experience

Tailored Healthcare Staffing Registered Nurse February 2020 - Present (6 months)

Novant Health
Critical Care Registered Nurse
October 2018 - February 2020 (1 year 5 months)
Greensboro/Winston-Salem, North Carolina Area

Neurosurgical Intensive Care Unit

Tailored Healthcare Staffing
Travel RN
March 2018 - October 2018 (8 months)

Stepdown ICU and Progressive Care in North Carolina, MO

Atlas MedStaff
Travel Nurse
September 2016 - October 2018 (2 years 2 months)
Greater St. Louis and Kansas City area

Registered Nurse in Midwest region, MO, AK, IL- Telemetry and Stepdown/ Respiratory care units

Grandview Healthcare Center

Page 1 of 3

Charge RN

October 2013 - September 2016 (3 years)

Washington, MO

Post-Acute/Skilled Rehabilitation nursing/IV therapy/Administrative Clinical Support team member

SSM St. Joseph Hospital West

Staff RN

September 2014 - April 2015 (8 months)

Medical Surgical Nursing with emphasis on Orthopedic surgical nursing

Compassionate Nursing Services

Private Duty RN

August 2012 - January 2015 (2 years 6 months)

11710 Administration Dr., Suite 48

Providing in-home, private duty services to clients who have undergone surgery and/or rehabilitation.

Behavior Intervention Services

Personal Care Assistant

November 2010 - August 2012 (1 year 10 months)

- Supporting clients within the Autism spectrum in natural home and Independent Supported Living (ISL) milieu with the goal of reducing maladaptive behaviors and fostering increased independence in clients' daily living.
- Responsibility in implementing Behavior Support Plan (BSP) and a Personal Care Plan (PCP) under supervision of a Board-Certified Behavior Analyst.

Education

Guilford Technical Community College

Doctoral, Family Practice Nurse/Cardiology subspecialty · (2019 - 2020)

Southeast Missouri State University

Bachelor's degree, Nursing Practice · (2014 - 2017)

St. Charles Community College

Associate of Science (A.S.), Nursing Practice · (2011 - 2013)

St. Louis Community College-Meramec

General transfer studies, Liberal Arts and Sciences, General Studies and Humanities \cdot (2004 - 2004)